It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy!
Family Guy 10x21 Tea Peter
茶皮特
中文字幕:wudixny 校对:zurica 注释:wudixny
后期:wudixny 压制:wudixny  @familyguy贴吧字幕组
喔 祝贺你的店重新开张 Mort
Wow, congratulations on your grand re-opening, Mort.
看起来你的顾客都回来了
Looks like your customers are comin' back.
谢谢 Lois  再次开张抢钱的感觉棒极了
Thanks, Lois. It's good to be up and gouging again.
噢 当心 小心你的脚下 Brian
Oh, careful. Watch out there, Brian.
地看上去是湿的
Looks like the floor is wet.
抱歉 我赶时间
Excuse me. I'm kind of in a hurry
妈了个巴子
Son of a bitch!
天啊 你还好吧
Oh, my God! Are you okay?
不好意思 我最近有点心不在焉
I'm sorry. I've been a little distracted lately.
我觉得我老婆最近总和另一个男人一起过马路
I think my wife has been crossing the street with another man.
天 我希望Alan不会发现
God, I hope Alan doesn't find out.
嘿 别想那个蠢货了
Hey, forget that klutz.
嗯 也许该买这个
Hmm, maybe this one.
嘿 看上去很正常 对不
Hey. Lookin' at you pretty normal, huh?
才怪
No!
啊 奶奶的
Aw, fudge.
等等 我知道了
Wait, I know!
我会想出办法的
I'll figure this out.
身体各部件都还在老地方
Th-the pieces are all there.
我要回家好好想个办法
I-I'll go home and figure this out.
啊 酷毙了 嘿 Mort 这是什么
Aw, cool. Hey Mort, what's this thing?
哦 那个? 那是我的"欢迎光临 我们正在营业"的招牌
Oh, that? That's my "Come In! We're Open" sign.
什么东西 和iPad一样吗
What's that, like an iPad?
不 是个招牌
No, it's a sign.
真希望我也有一个
Wish I had one of those.
我有一整箱呢
I've got a whole box of them.
拿去吧 送你了 不要钱
Take it. It's yours. No charge.
呃 典型的犹太人啊
Ugh, typical Jew.
今秋上映
TV ANNOUNCER:Coming this fall
由《失踪的宝贝》制片人打造
from the producers of Gone Baby Gone,
的精彩续集
comes the riveting sequel:
《失踪的严重残疾宝贝》
Gone Severely Disabled Baby Gone.
我向你们保证会找回你们的女儿
I promise you we are going to find your daughter.
好吧 但 你-你尽力而为吧
Okay, but, you know, do-do what you can,
但是说真的 不要 呃 把自己弄死了
but seriously, don't, like, kill yourself.
噢 如果你找到她 把这喇叭按几下
Oh, and if you do find her, honk this horn a couple times.
这是让她唯一不咬你的办法
It's the only way to get her to stop biting you.
我再重申一下 慢慢来
But again, no rush.
Peter 你干嘛呢
Peter, what are you doing?
我只是把新招牌挂起来
I'm just putting up my new sign.
别把那个放我们门上
Don't put that thing on our door.
如果你想挂起来
If you want to hang it somewhere,
就挂到地下室好了
hang it in the basement.
噢 为什么 这样你洗衣服的时候就能独占它了么
Oh, why? So you can hog it while you're doing laundry?
- 没门 - Peter 我们可不是做生意的
- No way. - Peter, we're not a business.
嘿 我看到你的招牌了 这么说 你们在营业?
Hey, I saw your sign. So, you're open?
- 没错 - 你们是卖什么的
- That's right. - What do you do?
- 你需要什么 - 牛奶
- What do you need? - Milk.
这个我们有
We have milk.
Peter 我告诉过你 我不喜欢
Peter, I told you, I don't like
这些陌生人在我们家里乱走
all these strangers walking around in our house.
他们不是陌生人 Lois 他们是我们宝贵的顾客
They're not strangers, Lois; they are our valued customers.
而且如果不向他们表明我们对忠实顾客的感激
And if we don't show them we appreciate their loyalty,
- 他们就会去别家店子了 - 什么
- they're gonna go someplace else. - For what?!
不想惊动任何人
Not to alarm anyone,
但有个人把我带到衣柜里
but some guy took me in the closet
试穿了我(汗...)
and tried me on.
她说的没错 爸 这根本就没有意义啊
She's right, Dad. None of this makes any sense.
Meg 你给我去休息10分钟
Meg, go take your ten.
你最好明白这是一次口头警告
And you may consider this a verbal warning.
Peter 我想让这些人离开
Peter, I want these people to leave.
对了 我很合身(再汗...)
I fit, by the way.
Lois 我最爱的就是
Lois, I'd love nothing more
坐在这和你一起聊天了
than to sit here and chat with you,
但我有生意要忙呢
but I have a business to run.
你们好 有什么可以帮忙的
Hi there. May I help you folks?
是这样 我们家想要一张肖像画
Yes, my family and I would like our portrait painted.
那你们就来对地方了
Well, you came to the right place.
看着很不错
Looking good.
快完成了
Almost done.
然后…好了
And... there.
大功告成
Done.
你都画了些什么呀
What have you done?!
我画的是事实
I painted the truth.
我画的是我眼中的事实
I painted my truth.
转一圈瞧瞧 甜心
Gimme a spin, sweetie.
你觉得怎样啊 马麻
What do you think, Mom?
是不是你迄今见过最好看的新娘啊
Is that the most beautiful bride you've ever seen?
我爱死了
I love it!
噢 但这实在是很贵
Oh, it's just so much money.
没错 说的对
It's true. It's true.
把衣服脱下来吧 甜心
Take the dress off, sweetheart.
你妈说你不能拥有它了
Your mother says you can't have it.
等-等等 再等一下
W-wait, wait, wait a minute.
你真的很喜欢么
Do you really love it?
是的 感觉就是为我量身打造的婚纱
I do. It just feels like my wedding dress.
噢 马麻 她喜欢它
Oh, Mom, she loves it.
好 我们要了
Okay. We'll take it.
Peter 那女孩穿着我的婚纱干嘛呢
Peter, what is that girl doing in my wedding dress?!
- 她走了么 - 没
- She gone? - No.
好 那既然我就在下面
Okay, well, while I'm down here
我就把我的名片给你吧
let me give you my card.
放进去了
There you go.
给你 半磅枫蜜火鸡 片好了的
Here you go. A half pound of honey maple turkey, sliced thin.
可我是想配一把钥匙
I wanted a duplicate key made.
你已经有把上好的了
You have a good one.
噢 嘿 Joe 怎么了
Oh, hey, Joe. What's going on?
Peter 我恐怕要来关掉你的店了
Peter, I'm afraid I'm here to shut you down.
你现在是无照经营
You're running an unlicensed business,
这违反了法律
and that's against the law.
噢 法律就是狗屎
Aw, that is such bullcrap.
但你不能和市政府对着干
Well, you can't fight City Hall.
噢 那我们走着瞧
Oh, we'll see about that!
市政府会空手道
City Hall knows karate.
抱歉了 Peter 政府制定了法规
I'm sorry, Peter, but the government makes the rules.
我只是执行而已
I just enforce them.
我不敢相信 Joe
I don't believe this, Joe.
这就好比生活在俄罗斯
This is like living in Russia.
我还不如直接搬去那算了
I might as well just move there.
你一定不想那么做的
You don't want to do that.
那里阴暗 寒冷 而且约炮
It's dark; it's cold; and hooking up
完全靠运气 因为他们都穿大外套
is just a crapshoot 'cause of all the big coats.
好了 数到3一起脱外套
All right, drop the coats on three.
1… 2…
One... two...
three!
- 吔 - 呃
- Yeah!- Oh...
嘿 你有没有不小心用过
Hey, you ever accidentally masturbate
你妈年轻时的照片打飞机
to young pictures of your mom?
哪个傻逼会这样开始聊天的
Who the (bleep) starts a conversation like that?
我刚坐下来呢
I just sat down.
天 你怎么了 Peter
Geez, what's your problem, Peter?
抱歉 Quagmire
I'm sorry, Quagmire.
我还在难过那狗日的政府
I'm still just upset about the damn government
搅黄了我的生意
sticking its nose in my business.
我听说了
I hear ya.
我们的税款都给浪费在荒唐的原因上了
Wasting our tax dollars on ridiculous causes.
我们还得保护白头海雕?
We gotta protect bald eagles?
美国国鸟 曾经濒危 通过保育已无灭绝之虞
白头海雕应有权自己做出选择
Bald eagles should be allowed to make their own decisions!
宝贝 我不在乎你秃不秃
Honey, I don't care that you're bald.
白头海雕的"bald"源自英文旧词"piebald"(黑白相间) 和"bald"(秃)没关系
我还是觉得你很有魅力
I find you just as attractive.
不是你的缘故
It's not about you.
是关于我作为一个鹰建筑师的自信
It's about my confidence as an eagle architect.
为鹰类独家定制 将给你
ANNOUNCER:Just for Eagles will give you
更密实 丰满 自然的头发
thicker, fuller,more natural hair...
这样你就能专注于你的雄鹰事业了
so you can just focus on eagle stuff.
你真是个出色的建筑师
You're an excellent architect.
该死的政府
Freakin' government.
把所有的好水管都给了消防员
Giving all the good hoses to firemen.
我想要那些水管
I want them hoses.
晚上好 我是Tom Tucker
ANCHORMAN:Good evening, I'm Tom Tucker.
我是Joyce Kinney
And I'm Joyce Kinney.
接下来是 孤独症:
Coming up: Autism:
是真实的或者只是
Is it real or just another excuse
孩子们不以礼待人的另一借口
for kids these days to forget their manners?
但首先 成千上万人期待着
But first, thousands are expected
明天的茶党集会
for tomorrow's Tea Party rally
庆祝他们在Quahog新成立的总部
celebrating their new Quahog headquarters.
没错 Joyce
That's right, Joyce.
茶党已经取得了大量的支持者
The Tea Party has gained a sizable following
因为他们所要求的低税收
based on their message of low taxes,
有限政府 还有 生日快乐 Tom
limited government, and happy birthday, Tom...
有限政府是指政府自身在规模 职能 权力和
行为方式上受到法律和社会的严格限制和有效制约
天啊 你们这些家伙
Oh, my God, you guys!
茶党 是吧?
Tea Party, huh?
其实 我也想参加个什么运动
Well, I'd like to be part of a movement,
但是什么运动会想要一个生气的胖子
but what movement would want an angry fat guy
还有一大堆别人讨厌听到的意见呢
with a lot of opinions who hates listening?
想知道更多关于茶党平台的信息
For more details on the Tea Party platform,
我们现在就带你看看这场超级盛大的焰火秀
we now go to this totally boss fireworks show.
天啊 我所信奉的就是这一切啊
Oh, my God! That's everything I believe in!
他们为什么要从我们这剥夺这些
Why are they trying to take that away from us?
没错
I hear ya.
好吧 就这样了
Well, that's it.
我明天要去茶党集会
I am going down to that rally tomorrow
然后加入他们
and I am joining the Tea Party!
噢 等等 我们的男性针织俱乐部也在那个时候活动
Oh, wait, that's the same time as my men's knitting club,
虽然他们最近对我很苛刻
although they have been really critical lately.
你还是没有在诚实的针织 Peter
You're still not knitting honestly, Peter.
你只是想让我们喜欢你才针织的
You're knitting like you want us to like you.
你不是真心的
It's not coming from inside.
完全停留在表面
It's very superficial.
谢谢你 你让我轻松地做好了决定
Thank you! You've made my decision easier!
对 就是那样 像那样针织
Yes! That! Knit that!
各位 向茶党说早上好吧
Good Tea Party morning, everyone!
Peter 你居然加入了茶党
Peter, you joined the Tea Party?!
没错 Brian
That's right, Brian.
我周六终于有了更好的事情可以做
I finally got something better to do
而不是坐在商场里
with my Saturdays than sit at the mall
看日本小妞因为普通的谈话就发笑
and watch Japanese girls laugh at normal conversation.
然后 我今天早上开车上的班
So, I drove to work this morning...
然后我停下来买了杯咖啡
And I had to stop for coffee.
然后 我家附近有个星巴克
So, there's a Starbucks near my house.
你们整个就一个马戏团
You people are a circus.
我终于参加了一个正常的运动
Finally, I'm part of a movement of regular people
来夺回我们的政权
trying to take back our government.
听着 茶党不是你
Look, the Tea Party isn't
想当然的什么草根运动
the grassroots movement you think it is.
草根运动是指一种非常规从低层势力而启发的运动
其实是由大型财团自主地
It's actually funded by Big Business types
他们只是利用你们来摆脱政府的阻挠
who are using you to get the government out of their way
这样他们就能蹂躏所有人了
so they can roll over everyone.
今天早上妈妈在加油站和一个女人牵手了
Mom held hands with a woman at the gas station this morning.
不知道那到底是啥意思 只是报告一声
Don't know what that means. Just reporting it.
我只是想说你正在被利用
All I'm saying is you're being used
而且你又太无知不知就里
and you're too clueless to know it.
哇 你觉得你真是高人一等 是吧
Boy, you just think you're so superior, don't you?
就像第一个在陆地上行走的生物一样
Like that first creature to walk on dry land.
嘿 你去哪了
Hey, where'd you go?
- 啊 我去慢跑了一会儿 - 什么是慢跑
- Ah, I went for a jog. - What's a jog?
是一种能让你保持好身材的方法 就是这样
It's a great way to stay in shape is what it is.
就像游泳?
Is it like a swim?
不 不 这 这完全和游泳不是一回事儿
No, no, it's, it's nothing like a swim.
喔 今天来这的人好多
Wow, a lot of people here today.
是啊 伙计 我爱街头集市
Yeah. Man, I love street fairs.
他们有坐的 玩的
They got rides, games,
还有美国白人做出来难吃的民族风味食物
and ethnic food cooked horribly by white Americans.
玉米饼 这里有热乎的玉米饼
Tack-os! Hot tack-os here!
噢 这是玉米饼么
Oh, are those tack-os?
你最好相信它们是
You better believe they're tack-os.
我爱玉米饼
I love tack-os!
尤其是在玉米粉圆饼上的
Especially on a corn tor-tilla.
噢 我爱有玉米饼的玉米粉圆饼
Oh! I love tack-os on a corn tor-tilla!
哇 他们居然真的反对社会主义
Boy, they're really against socialism.
是啊 茶党的主旨就是自力更生
That's right. The Tea Party is all about self-reliance.
看 那边甚至还有个自爱隧道
Look, there's even a Tunnel of Self-Love.
你想买一张自己游览中的照片么 先生
Would you like to buy a photo of yourself on the ride, sir?
不 不要了
No, I would not.
欢迎大家
Welcome, everyone!
很高兴看到有这么多普通人在这儿
It's great to see so many regular people out here.
那些厌倦了大政府
Folks who are tired of big government
大政府指奉行干预主义政策的政府 一般被理解为意味着经济管理与社会控制
准备站起来为自己权利反抗的人们
and are ready to stand up for their rights.
耶 打倒滥花钱的民主党
Yeah! Down with the Spend-o-crats!
加油 马歇尔
PETER:We are Marshall!
这句口号源于于美马歇尔大学的橄榄球员和教练死于飞机失事
后被改编成电影
现在 我很荣幸
And now, it's my privilege
给大家介绍另一位普通的蓝领朋友
to introduce another regular, blue-collar guy,
我们Quahog分部的发言人 Joe Workingman(劳动者)
our Quahog chapter spokesman: Joe Workingman!
下午好 朋友们 社会经济界的同僚们
Good afternoon, friends and socioeconomic equals!
还有谁没厌倦政府的这套鬼把戏吗
Is anyone else out there sick of government crap?
天哪
Oh, my God.
感觉他每一句都说到了我心坎上
It's like he's saying everything I'm listening to.
没错啊
That's right.
政府想告诉你该吃什么食物
The government wants to tell you what foods to eat.
该去什么教堂
And what church you can go to.
而且你不能养黑猩猩
And that you can't own a chimpanzee
因为你没有足够的责任心
because you're not responsible enough.
我会好好喂养它的
I would feed it!
政府还想告诉你
Also, the government wants to tell you
你能有几个孩子
how many children you can have.
什么 不
What?! No!
政府还想告诉你
And the government wants to tell you
你不能往河里扔旧电视
you can't throw your old TVs into the river.
那我上哪找电视去
Then how I supposed to find TV?
如果你加入了茶党 众志成城 我们就能改变这一切
If you join the Tea Party, together, we can fix all that.
但你们肯定不想参加茶党
But you probably don't wanna join the Tea Party
因为你们都会得到这些又傻又酷的钥匙链
because all you get are these stupid, awesome keychains!
天哪 这就是我梦寐以求的钥匙链
Oh, my God, it's the keychain from the dream!
我得说这人说的很有道理
I got to say that guy made a lot of sense.
那是当然 政府现在真的已经失控了
He sure did. The government's really gotten outta hand.
是啊 那些坏蛋把一切都给毁了
Yeah, those bastards have ruined everything.
就和乡下人毁了各种聚在一起的
The same way the Village People ruined any gathering
警察 印第安酋长和建筑工人
of a cop, an Indian chief, and a construction worker.
应召牛郎的角色扮演么...
天啊 我们和你们合个影不
Oh, my God, can we get a picture with you guys?
我们不是那种人
We're not those guys.
是啊 离我们远点
Yes, please leave us alone.
我们忙着呢
We're very busy.
现在 我们说到哪了 哦 对
Now, where were we? Oh, yeah.
我们得解决那个
We've gotta solve that security problem
正在建设的印第安赌场的保安问题
for the Indian Casino we're constructing.
嘿 你们想去醉蚌酒吧么
Hey, you guys want to head to the Clam?
我待会会赶上你们的 我得去个厕所
I'll catch up with you. I got to hit the john.
嘿 伙计 这附近有洗手间么
Hey, buddy. Is there a bathroom around here,
或者一个二楼窗户
or a second floor window?
Carter?!
噢 嘿
Oh... hey.
你和茶党有来往?
You're involved with the Tea Party?
等一会
Wait a minute.
这就是Brian警告我的
This is what Brian was warning me about:
茶党是由有钱人操纵的
that the Tea Party is run by rich guys
他们只会为自己着想
who are only out for themselves.
Brian?
你是说你们那个自大的没工作的狗
You mean that arrogant, unemployed dog of yours?
Peter 他就是个自由派的中坚分子
Peter, he's just one of those liberal elites
喜欢散布谣言而且讨厌爱国者
who spreads lies and hates patriots.
是 有点
Yeah, he kinda is.
但我和你都是实业家 我们努力工作交纳赋税
You and I are both businessmen who work hard and pay taxes.
除了我是你的一万倍之外
Except that I make 10,000 times what you make.
是啊 我们是一样的 你和我
Yeah, we're the same, you and me.
知道么 Peter  事实是
You know, Peter, the truth is,
我可以用到一个像你这样的普通人
I could actually use a regular guy like you
来帮忙传达我们的信息
to help get our message out,
而且我知道 Joe Workingman也会同意的
and I know Joe Workingman agrees with me.
欢迎你入伙 Peter
Love to have you on board, Peter.
哇 谢了 Joe 我你就放心吧
Wow, thanks, Joe. You can count on me.
啊 Carter 你刚错过了Joe Workingman
Aw, Carter, you just missed Joe Workingman.
噢 我想他知道我刚才来过
Oh, I think he'll know I was here.
我不太确定发生了什么
I'm not sure what's happening.
噢 嗨 Peter 你的集会如何
Oh, hi, Peter. How was your rally?
噢 棒极了 而且现在我知道
Oh, it was great, and now I know
支持这件事的正确原因了
it's the right cause to get behind
因为像你爸这样的聪明人也参与了
'cause a smart guy like your dad is involved.
什么 Carter去了茶党集会
What, Carter was at the Tea Party rally?
是啊 整个就是他在运作的
Yeah, he was running the whole thing.
Peter 我是怎么跟你说那些有钱人的
Peter, what did I tell you about rich guys?
听着 我知道你在想什么 Brian
Look, I know what you're thinking, Brian,
但是别担心 没事的
but don't worry; it's all okay.
其实你才是我们的对头
Turns out you're the enemy.
他们是和我们一边的
They're the ones who are on our side.
噢 当然 Carter Pewterschmidt
Oh, of course, Carter Pewterschmidt,
一个在本市拥有炼油厂的企业家
an industrialist with oil refineries in this city,
和你是一边的
is on your side.
他想要废除环境法规
He wants to get rid of environmental regulations
为了你
for you.
Brian 他不懂讽刺
Brian, he doesn't get sarcasm.
不 不只是环境法规 Ban
No, it's not just environmental regulations, Ban.
Carter 想要消灭
Carter wants to get rid
Quahog的整个市政府
of the whole city government of Quahog.
他甚至让我负责这个运动的公关宣传
He even put me in charge of the PR campaign to do it.
消灭政府?
Get rid of the government?
Peter  假如我没猜错自己的老爸 那他肯定是在利用你
Peter, if I know my dad, he's probably using you.
Lois 我很高兴你把碗都洗了
Lois, I'm so glad you're done with the dishes
这样你就能过来瞎晃悠 然后对这事添油加醋帮个腔
so that you can hang out and chime in on this.
事实上 Peter 我没有洗碗
Actually, Peter, I haven't done the dishes.
噢 你没有么
Oh, you haven't?
那我就不明白了
Well, then, I'm confused.
噢 他确实懂讽刺
Oh, he does get sarcasm.
好了 现在记住
All right, now, remember,
茶党是一个草根运动
the Tea Party is a grassroots movement.
我们并不靠那些垃圾的主流媒体报道
We're not covered by the lame stream media,
所以我们要分别接触每个普通人
so we got to reach out to the common man individually.
好的 普通人(男人)
Right, common man.
你好
WOMAN:Hello.
啊 天 这是…这是个女孩
Ah, geez, it's... it's a girl.
我能和这家的男主人说话么
May I speak to the man of the house?
我是这家的女主人 而且我家没有男人
This is the woman of the house, and there is no man living here.
没有?
No?
怎-怎么…我…那你怎么付电话费
W-W-What is... I-I... how are you paying for this phone?
我是个律师
I'm a lawyer.
哦 我明白了 你现在正在你那小法庭上
Oh, I see, and are you in your little courthouse
代表芭比娃娃出庭么
right now representing Barbie?
好了 茶党一票
Okay, one vote for the Tea Party.
好极了 和政府吻别吧
All right, kiss government good-bye.
嗯 我等不及要把所有的市政府公务猿都炒掉
Yeah, I can't wait to fire all them city employees,
从那个半睡半醒的建筑工人开始
starting with that half-asleep construction worker.
搞毛啊
What the hell?
到-到底是哪个-- 停还是走
W-W-Which one is it-- stop or go forward?
这差别可大了
This is a big deal.
他们一点也不一样
They're not at all similar.
啊 不 不 不 不
Ah, no, no, no, no.
先生 你已经失去我的信任了
You, sir, have lost my business.
(扬基曲"Yankee Doodle Dandy")
Peter几人的打扮恶搞了Archibald Willard的油画Spirit of '76
他们在S03E04中也这样打扮过
(解散市政府)
大伙们 正事要紧
People, please, first things first.
这里有人是在Craigslist网上来买沙发的么
Is there anyone here for the couch off of Craigslist?
一个大型免费分类广告网站
我是
I am.
好的 进来吧
Oh, good, come on in.
这和Craigslist网上的图片一模一样
That is the picture from Craigslist.
完全不是
No way it is.
就是的
It is.
根本不是
No way it is.
好吧 你们剩下的想干什么
All right, what do the rest of you want?
我们想要市政府关闭
We want the city government shut down.
哦 我明白了
Oh, I see.
你们都是这么想的么
And all of you feel the same way?
- 是的 - 不
- Yes! - No!
是的
Yes!
那好 我除了公仆就什么也不是了
Well, I'm nothing if not a public servant,
既然大众们都已经表了态
and the public has made its feelings known.
我由此正式宣布 Quahog市政府解散
I hereby declare Quahog's city government disbanded.
我很荣幸之前一直为你们服务 现在我要离开了
It has been my pleasure to serve you, and now I take my leave.
这根柱子是我的
This column is mine.
我从家里带过来的
I brought it from home.
下午好 我是Tom Tucker
Good afternoon, I'm Tom Tucker.
重要新闻: Quahog现在已经完全处于无政府状态了
Our top story: Quahog is now completely government-free,
这意味着我可以无视直播条例了
which means I'm free of all broadcast regulations,
所以我这个播报员再也不用去洗手间了
so no more trips to the bathroom for this reporter,
只需一个大屁股咖啡罐放在桌下即可
just a big-ass coffee can under the desk.
家人们 你们好
Hello, family.
Peter 你刚在外面搞什么飞机呢
Peter, what the hell were you doing out there?
知道么 我已厌倦这些年来一直从路上回来了
You know, for years I've been sick of taking the roads home,
所以今天我从院子上开回来的
so today I took the yards.
一个路灯都没撞到
Didn't hit one light.
天 没有政府的束缚
Man, getting rid of the government has been
是这里这么久以来最爽的事了
the best thing to happen around here in a long time.
没错
That's right.
没有政府我就可以随便嗑墨司卡林
Without government I'm free to take a lot of mescaline
一种致幻药
然后开车去拉斯维加斯了
and drive to Vegas.
恶搞了小说《恐惧拉斯维加斯》的封面 有同名电影
等你在舞台上见到黛比•雷诺兹就知道了
Wait till you see Debbie Reynolds on stage.
美国演员 主演过《雨中曲》等片 现已80岁高龄
是啊 现在我和我的西班牙语老师
Yeah, and now my Spanish teacher and I
终于可以在走廊里牵手了
can finally hold hands in the halls.
(西)Meg 图书馆在哪
¿Meg, dónde está la biblioteca?
因为我准备在图书馆里啪啪啪你
Because I'm going to bang you in the biblioteca.
我很高兴你们都很享受你们的自由
Well, I'm glad you're all enjoying your freedom,
但你们最近往窗外看过么
but have you taken a look out the window lately?
那是什么
What is that?
那些烟都是从哪来的
Where's all that smoke coming from?
那是Pewterschmidt工业的炼油厂
The Pewterschmidt Industries refinery,
而且那不是烟 是一大片污染之云
and it's not smoke; it's a giant cloud of pollution.
上帝啊
Oh, my God.
如果它经过那片坏街区到我们这儿
If that gets past the bad neighborhoods and reaches us,
那我麻烦就大了
that's going to be a big problem.
他们不能这么做
They can't do that.
我们应该举报他们
We should report them.
给谁 现在都没有政府了
To who? There's no government.
那就只能靠我们自己 人民群众们 来解决了
Then it's up to us, the people, to find a solution.
关上窗帘
Close the curtains.
啊 茶党
Ah, Tea Party.
妈的 这就是我一直害怕会发生的事
Damn it, this is what I was afraid was going to happen.
这座城市要变成地狱了
This town is going to go to hell.
我现在宣布你们为夫妇
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
你可以吻新娘了
You may kiss the bride.
我真高兴我们等待了
I'm glad we waited.
9个月后
Giraffity.
giraffe(长颈鹿)和giggity的合体
嗯 看到没 这不是我的种
Yeah, see, that's not mine.
嘿 Mort 你怎么变成金发了
Hey, Mort, what gives with the blond hair?
是啊 你看起来怪怪的
Yeah, you look weird like that.
历史上 大规模骚乱中
Historically, in instances of mass lawlessness,
他们首先做的就是围捕犹太人
the first thing they do is round up the Jews.
打扰 雅利安朋友 你有没有在附近看到犹太人
Excuse me, fellow Aryan, have you seen any Jews around?
纳粹白人至上种族主义标准是指金发碧眼的白种人就是雅利安人
有奖励么
Is there a reward?
等一会 你是犹太人?
Wait a minute. Are you Jewish?
我是指 呃 公然在更衣室里裸体
I mean, uh, unashamed locker room nudity.
这家伙挺符合犹太教律的
This guy's kosher.
说漏了
Oops.
抓住他
Let's get him!
下午好 我是Tom Tucker
Good afternoon, I'm Tom Tucker.
Quahog在无政府状态下已经第五天了
It's day five of the new government-less Quahog,
现在我穿着T恤衫
and I'm wearing a T-shirt.
Tom 我不认为政府
Tom, I don't think the government
要求过你穿西装的
was requiring you to wear a suit.
但他们阻止过我打你的脸
Well, they were stopping me from punching you in the face.
你想这样么
Is that what you want?
算了 告诉你 你知道么
No, you know what? You know what?
- 把你的钱包给我 - 什么
- Give me your wallet. - What?
你听到我的话了 我说把你的钱包给我
You heard me, I said give me your wallet.
真是个蹩脚的钱包
This is a crappy wallet.
全是些烂玩意儿
You have bad stuff.
嗷 搞毛呀
Oh, what the hell?
Lois 电视又没了
Lois, the TV went off again.
是电没了 Peter
It's the electricity, Peter.
电线都坏了 但是没有人去修理他们
There are power lines down, and there's no one to fix 'em.
警察也不出现了 厕所也不能冲水了
The cops don't come, the toilets don't flush,
而且街上满满的都是垃圾
and there's garbage piling up in the streets.
瑞安·菲利普都放出来好多天了
Ryan Phillippe's been out there for days.
美国演员 出演过《我知道去年夏天你干了什么》等片
有人想要被受精么
Would anyone like to be impregnated?
2010前女友与他分手后几个月后发现怀上了他的孩子
我们曾有一座美好的小镇 Peter
We had a nice town, Peter.
我曾有一段美好的人生
I had a nice life,
但你和你的反政府伙计们把这都毁了
but you and your antigovernment buddies ruined it.
嘿 那你现在你们的茶党怎么样了 嗯?
Hey, so how's that Tea Party going, huh?
更像 T.P.党了
More like T.P. Party.
厕纸
Toilet paper.
我不知道发生了什么事 Brian
I don't know what happened, Brian.
索马里在无政府状态下就挺好的
Not having a government worked great in Somalia,
但某种意义上我们是把这完全搞砸了
but somehow we seem to have botched it all up.
确实如此
Looks that way.
等会 也许有方法能解决这问题
Wait a minute. There might be a way out of this.
什么
What?
我们只要和让我们变成这样的人谈谈就行了
We just talk to the guy who got us into this.
他会知道该怎么办的
He'll know what to do.
Pewterschmidt先生 Pewterschmidt先生
Mr. Pewterschmidt. Mr. Pewterschmidt.
走开
Go away.
但是 Pewterschmidt先生 你得做点什么
But, Mr. Pewterschmidt, you got to do something.
路上的坑洼再也没人补了
The potholes ain't getting fixed no more.
交通信号灯也不工作了
The stoplights ain't working.
卫生棉广告也不在他们的示范里用蓝色液体了
Tampon commercials no longer use blue liquids in their demonstrations.
让它是蓝色的吧 一直都是这样啊
Make it blue. That's always been the deal!
你们想给我们看什么都可以 但是必须得是蓝色啊
You show whatever you want, but you make it blue!
求你了 你一定要帮我们
Come on. You got to help us out.
去死吧
Go to hell.
我想他是不会帮我们的 Peter
I don't think he's going to help, Peter.
但如果有钱人不照应我们 还有谁会呢
But if rich people aren't looking out for us, who is?
那也许我们得互相照应了
Well, maybe we need to look out for each other.
走吧 Brian 是时候让事情走向正轨了
Come on, Brian. It's time to make this right.
等等 你们离开前 往左边走两步
Wait, before you go, take two steps to the left.
往上看
Look up.
好了 笑一个
Okay, smile.
啊 我真烂
Aw, I suck.
Quahog的乡亲们 我有些话要说
People of Quahog, I have something to say.
既然我们已经把自己
Now that we've freed ourselves
从政府的可怕桎梏中解放出来了
from the terrible shackles of government,
是时候用一个更好的东西取代它了
it's time to replace it with something better.
首先我们需要一套规则体系
The first thing we need is a system of rules
所有人都应当遵守
that everyone must live by.
必须得有规则
Got to have rules.
既然我们不能把所有的时间都花在制定规则上
And since we can't spend all our time making rules,
我想我们应该选出一些人来代表我们
I think that we should elect some people to represent us,
他们来带我们制定规则和选择
and they should make rules and choices on our behalf.
这应该是个好主意
That's probably a good idea.
现在 这个可能要花不少钱 所以我提议:
Now, this may be kind of expensive, so I got a plan:
每人都要从他们每年的工资当中拿出点钱
everyone should have to give some money from their salaries each year.
穷人可以出一点点
Poor people will give a little bit of money
富人要出一大笔钱
and rich people will give a larger amount of money,
然后我们的代表就会用这些钱
and our representatives will use all that money
来雇佣人向我们提供
to hire some people who will then provide us
社会秩序和基础服务
with social order and basic services.
呃 这里一件我想要的衬衫都没有
Ugh, there's not one shirt I wish I had out there.
这不会很完美
Now, it won't be perfect.
有些代表可能最终会变得很混
Some of our representatives may end up being bastards.
但是你知道么 那也可以
But you know what? That's okay
因为之后我们就会有更多的选举
'cause later we're going to have more elections,
然后我们就能用这些选举来让那些坏蛋们下台
and we can use those elections to get rid of the bad guys
用好人取而代之
and replace 'em with good guys,
然后这个体系就会一直继续下去
and then the system will just keep going on and on
就像那样
just like that.
那么有人支持我么
So who's with me?
你们愿意加入我一起尝试这疯狂的玩意儿么
Will you join me in trying this new crazy thing?
那我们说干就干吧
Then let's do it.
耶 我们在没有政府的情况下做成了
Yeah, and we did it all without government.
我真为你自豪 Peter
I'm very proud of you, Peter.
噢 Lois 这对我来说没什么
Oh, Lois, that means nothing to me.
我唯一关心的就是他们在网上留言板上说的话了
I only care what they say on the Internet message boards.
中文字幕:wudixny 校对:zurica 注释:wudixny
后期:wudixny 压制:wudixny  @familyguy贴吧字幕组
好水管都给了消防员
Giving all the good hoses to firemen.
我想要那些水管
I want them hoses.
晚上好 我是Tom Tucker
ANCHORMAN:Good evening, I'm Tom Tucker.
我是Joyce Kinney
And I'm Joyce Kinney.
接下来是 孤独症:
Coming up: Autism:
是真实的或者只是
Is it real or just another excuse
孩子们不以礼待人的另一借口
for kids these days to forget their manners?
但首先 成千上万人期待着
But first, thousands are expected
明天的茶党集会
for tomorrow's Tea Party rally
庆祝他们在Quahog新成立的总部
celebrating their new Quahog headquarters.
没错 Joyce
That's right, Joyce.
茶党已经取得了大量的支持者
The Tea Party has gained a sizable following
因为他们所要求的低税收
based on their message of low taxes,
有限政府 还有 生日快乐 Tom
limited government, and happy birthday, Tom...
有限政府是指政府自身在规模 职能 权力和
行为方式上受到法律和社会的严格限制和有效制约
天啊 你们这些家伙
Oh, my God, you guys!
茶党 是吧?
Tea Party, huh?
其实 我也想参加个什么运动
Well, I'd like to be part of a movement,
但是什么运动会想要一个生气的胖子
but what movement would want an angry fat guy
还有一大堆别人讨厌听到的意见呢
with a lot of opinions who hates listening?
想知道更多关于茶党平台的信息
For more details on the Tea Party platform,
我们现在就带你看看这场超级盛大的焰火秀
we now go to this totally boss fireworks show.
天啊 我所信奉的就是这一切啊
Oh, my God! That's everything I believe in!
他们为什么要从我们这剥夺这些
Why are they trying to take that away from us?
没错
I hear ya.
好吧 就这样了
Well, that's it.
我明天要去茶党集会
I am going down to that rally tomorrow
然后加入他们
and I am joining the Tea Party!
噢 等等 我们的男性针织俱乐部也在那个时候活动
Oh, wait, that's the same time as my men's knitting club,
虽然他们最近对我很苛刻
although they have been really critical lately.
你还是没有在诚实的针织 Peter
You're still not knitting honestly, Peter.
你只是想让我们喜欢你才针织的
You're knitting like you want us to like you.
你不是真心的
It's not coming from inside.
完全停留在表面
It's very superficial.
谢谢你 你让我轻松地做好了决定
Thank you! You've made my decision easier!
对 就是那样 像那样针织
Yes! That! Knit that!
各位 向茶党说早上好吧
Good Tea Party morning, everyone!
Peter 你居然加入了茶党
Peter, you joined the Tea Party?!
没错 Brian
That's right, Brian.
我周六终于有了更好的事情可以做
I finally got something better to do
而不是坐在商场里
with my Saturdays than sit at the mall
看日本小妞因为普通的谈话就发笑
and watch Japanese girls laugh at normal conversation.
然后 我今天早上开车上的班
So, I drove to work this morning...
然后我停下来买了杯咖啡
And I had to stop for coffee.
然后 我家附近有个星巴克
So, there's a Starbucks near my house.
你们整个就一个马戏团
You people are a circus.
我终